belugapods.com 2011-11-01

# Beluga Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes Beluga's policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information. Beluga receives your information through our various web sites, SMS, APIs, services and third-parties ("Services"). When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country that you reside in or create information from, your information may be used by Beluga in the United States or any other country where Beluga operates.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@belugapods.com](mailto:privacy@belugapods.com). 

### Information Collection and Use

Tip We collect and use your information to provide our Services and improve them over time. 

**Information Collected Upon Registration:** When you create or reconfigure a Beluga account, you provide some personal information, such as your name, password, email address and picture. Some of this information, for example, your name and email address is available to anyone who is a member of one of your shared groups ("Pods"). This information is not displayed to the general public. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services or alert you to important events. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. 

**Pods, Updates and Photos:** Our Services are primarily designed to help you share information privately with your friends and colleagues. Most of the information you provide to us is information you are asking us to share with a small group of people ("a Pod"). This includes not only the messages you send ("Updates") and the metadata provided with Updates, such as the time the Update was sent, but also the Pods you create, the people you communicate with, the photos you share, and many other bits of information. None of the information you share with one Pod is ever automatically visible to members of another Pod or to the general public. However, please note that if information is shared with a Pod, and another member is later added to that Pod, all prior information shared with the Pod will be visible to the new member. 

**Location Information:** You may choose to note your location in your Updates. If you turn on location sharing, we may also save exact coordinates to help improve our service. You can control your location sharing settings on an individual Update basis. Location shared in an update is shared only with the Pod to which the Update is sent. 

**Log Data:** Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, the referring domain, pages visited, and search terms. Other actions, such as interactions with advertisements, may also be included in Log Data.

**Links:** Beluga may keep track of how you interact with links in Updates by redirecting clicks or through other means. We do this to help improve our Services, including advertising, and to be able to share aggregate click statistics such as how many times a particular link was clicked on.

**Cookies:** Like many websites, we use "cookies" to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services, and to authenticate users. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. Beluga may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

**Third Party Services:** Beluga uses a variety of services hosted by third parties to help provide our Services, such as providing alternate login options, and to help us understand the use of our Services, such as Google Analytics. These services may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP request.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Tip We do not disclose your private information except in the limited circumstances described here. 

**Your Consent:** We may share or disclose your information with your consent, such as when you use a third party web client to access your Beluga account.

**Service Providers:** We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to obligations mirroring the protections of this privacy policy.

**Law and Harm:** We may disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Beluga's rights or property.

**Business Transfers:** In the event that Beluga Inc. is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this privacy policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity.

**Non-Private or Non-Personal Information:** We may share or disclose aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as usage patterns or link click statistics

### Modifying Your Personal Information

If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools to access or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account.

### Our Policy Towards Children

Our Services are not directed to people under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at [privacy@belugapods.com](mailto:privacy@belugapods.com). We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

### Changes to this Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at http://belugapods.com/privacy. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via your Beluga client or to the email associated with your account. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

_This Privacy Policy is effective as of Sep. 23, 2010.  
Thoughts or questions about this Privacy Policy? Please, [let us know](mailto:privacy@belugapods.com). _
